Name: Mukul Sherekar msherek1

Module info: Module:14 / Final Exam  / Quantum Computation / 12/14/2021

Approach:

Main.py:
-Read the file using open and read and making sure file format and decoding is correct
-Once the file is read, all lines of contents will be in a list format
-Split content of each line by blank space to properly create list elements
-Run a simple for loop to figure out what letters are present and add them to the list
-Convert the number into float
-Create a numpy array for numbers
-Create a qubit object for each numpy array
-Apply operate function to transform (apply gates) the qubit
-Use try, except, pass to ignore any index error
-Finally print out the final state along with initial state and experiment method results

Operators.py:
-Create a class that instantiates a variable and raises an error if passed argument is not 
H or X

paulix.py and Hadamard.py:
-For these scripts, create a class which is a child class of singlequbit class. 
-Use super method 
-Create a method that uses matrix multiplication to convert the numpy array representing a qubit
-Print out the final state

Known bugs: 
-The script does not raise an exception when an invalid operator is passed and invalid probability amplitudes are passed on.
-The output is not precise i.e it prints out intermediate states and resulting probabilities. Ideally, script should print out
Only the final state and probabilities.